All they want to do is... Do it!!!
Kevin & Perry Go Large is a music, comedy film directed by Ed Bye.
When stubborn, spotty Kevin and his equally hopeless best friend Perry go on holiday to the party island Ibiza, they see
it as their big chance to become superstar club DJs and, more importantly, to lose their virginities.
But they aren't prepared for the interference of top DJ Eyeball Paul, not to
mention the embarrassment factor of Kevin's long-suffering parents.
Kevin, played by Harry Enfield.
Perry, played by Kathy Burke.
Eye Ball Paul, played by Rhys Ifans.
Dad, played by James Fleet.
Candice, played by Laura Fraser.
Anne Boleyn, played by Natasha Little.
Kevin & Perry Go Large is a 2000 British teen coming-of-age sex comedy
film based on the Harry Enfield sketch Kevin the Teenager.
The film was written by Dave Cummings and Harry Enfield and directed by Ed Bye.
Enfield, Kathy Burke and Louisa Rix all return to their roles
after previously appearing on Harry Enfield & Chums.
James Fleet replaced Stephen Moore as Kevin's father.
The film received mixed reviews but has since gained a cult following.
The film explores themes of puberty, first time,
virgin, becoming an adult, holiday.
The tone is lighthearted.